speedtest.com 2002-12-07

# Bandwidth Place, About Us

**About us**  

 **Privacy policy**  

At Bandwidth Place we understand that submitting information about yourself or business is serious. Out of respect for our customer's privacy, Bandwidth Place has developed the following privacy statement that discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. The purpose of this privacy policy is to let our users know what information of yours is collected through this web site, the organization collecting the information, how the information is used and with whom the information may be shared.

This policy may be updated at any time without notice. This policy applies only to the information collected by Bandwidth Place on our own web site.

 **Information collection and use**

Bandwidth Place is the sole owner of all information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Bandwidth Place collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

1.RFQ forms. The primary purpose of this collection is to provide that information to our affiliate partners for the purpose of the Request for Quote (RFQ) process. This includes your contact information and the particulars of your current and desired Internet connection. The RFQ form includes a number of required fields, which are essential for our affiliate partners to generate quotes. The form also contains a number of optional fields, which aid us and our affiliate partners in providing a more personalized and functional experience on our site. This information is passed on to our affiliate partners solely for the purposes of contact and quote generation and will not be used alternatively.

2.Other forms. Our site also contains various other forms including, but not limited to, our partnership information request form and our feedback forms. All these forms are used to gather information solely for our use.

3.Speed test. We store all the results of the speed test for our own statistical use.

4.Site stats. Our site uses various statistics software packages to measure our traffic and user demographics so that we can make our site the most useful it can be. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, diagnose problems with our servers, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and are used by us only.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Bandwidth Place uses optional cookies in our speed test and marketplace.

 **Links**

Bandwidth Place contains many links to other web sites. These links are provided for the utility of our customers only, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of this when they leave our site and to take the time to read the privacy policy of any web site requesting personal information.

|
